Mhm. Yeah, yeah.
Hello and welcome to Leah Ivana here,
Olive on Nora from the project prepared together.
The other can for an NGO,
which is offering classes for professional orientation than smaller than 30 years.
Basic computer classes, first aid and professional nursery language classes for
tourism, painting, farming or cooking.
Whatever is your interest.
We are sure that we have the right class for you.
Our professional teachers will be glad to get in touch with you
and help you to improve your knowledge,
find their phone numbers and the flyer.
You have a tent and contact them whenever you want to start.
Do not hesitate.
China's in our classes.
Get your certificate and learn something that will help you in your
future. We are looking forward to meeting you soon.